

Jesse Wells

designer + developer

jessewells.com/portfolio

About

Graphic Designer & Web Developer based in Brooklyn NY with 6+ years professional experience in digital design, print design, web design and front-end development

Likes

Vectors, SVG, Bezier Curves and everything Scalable & Lossless.

Web Components, Web Animation, CSS Grid, JAMstack.

PC, Microsoft, Adobe CC, Vue.js, Visual Studio Code, Pug, Stylus.

Contact

1263 Broadway Brooklyn NY 11221

jessenwells@gmail.com

347 243 5863



jessenwells



jessenwells

Work Experience

Modell's Sporting Goods Front End Developer

2016 - current

Assisted in all areas to redesign and relaunch the new Ecommerce site. Developed automated and streamlined

workflows.

Designed site specs, style guides and modern email templates.

Mammoth Advertising

2015 - 2016

Interactive Developer

Created interactive animated advertisements for web and display. Assisted in transition from flash to HTML5.

Everyday Media

2014 - 2015

Digital Designer

Designed and managed facebook advertisements and page graphics. Created promotional social media

campaigns.

Designed print ads, web ads, and HTML

emails.

F5 Interactive Agency

2012 - 2015

Front End Designer & Developer

Developed various projects involving front end templates, complex UI, interactive data, infographics and large scale animations.

Press Design

2010 - 2015

Senior Designer

Web Design, UI Design, Digital Design, Ecommerce, Wordpress.

Print Design, Branding, Apparel Graphics, Illustration, Animation.

Education

Fashion Institute of Technology

BFA - Illustration

Skills

Adobe Illustrator	\odot \odot \odot \odot	HTML5/CSS3	
Adobe Photoshop	\odot \odot \odot \odot	JavaScript / TypeScript	$ \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc \bigcirc$
Adobe InDesign	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	Vue js	
Adobe After Effects	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	React	
Adobe XD	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	Angular	\odot
Sketch / Figma	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	jQuery	\odot \odot \odot \odot
Wordpress	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	Node js	
Bootstrap / Foundation	\odot \odot \odot \odot	Gatsby js	\odot
SASS / SCSS	\odot \odot \odot \odot	GraphQL	\odot